# MAXWELL FRANK

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### **DETAILS**

PHONE

908-370-6530

**EMAIL** 

maxfrank13@gmail.com

LINKS

LinkedIn

<u>Github</u>

**Portfolio** 

**Twitter** 

#### **SKILLS**

Git

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

Bootstrap

jQuery

React

Node.js

## HOBBIES

Skateboarding Hiking

Music

## PROFILE

Lifetime creator with a background in woodworking and restaurant industries recently making a transition into Web Development. By utilizing my personal experience in these fields I am able to provide a unique perspective on the construction of web pages and applications. I find the logistical challenges that programming presents to be a motivating force in my experience as a developer.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Cook, Falafel Mafia

Portland, ME

Apr 2019 — Oct 2021

- · Cooking food to order in a fast-paced environment
- Preparing that food for its corresponding pick up (i.e. in-house, to-go, delivery, etc.)
- · Working on a food truck and experience with mobile food services
- · Assisting with catering operations
- · Assisting with management of employees and operations of a food truck

## Furniture Craftsman, Hanson Woodturning

Kennebunkport, ME

Feb 2017 — Feb 2019

- Use of milling machines to bring rough sawn lumber to a clean state of workability
- · Experience running a hydraulic lathe
- Prepping products for finishing through detail-oriented work
- · An understanding of press and clamp technologies

### Woodworker, Richardson Allen Furniture

Biddeford, ME

Aug 2016 — Dec 2016

- · Use of power tools and shop machines
- · Assisting with packing and shipping of final product
- · Use of spray gun to apply marine quality paint
- Eye for detail on finished product to ensure conformity with shop standards

## Manager's Assistant, Tito's Burriots & Wings

Summit, NJ

Aug 2010 — Aug 2014

- Served as an assistant to all administrative personnel and acted as a first point of contact for visitors and customers
- · General maintenance of the restaurant
- · Running catering operations and delivery

#### EDUCATION

## **Summit High School**

Summit, NJ

Sep 2007 — Jun 2011

· Senior Student Humanities Award, Summit High School, 2011

#### PERSONAL ACHIEVEMENTS

**Ultraskate** Homestead, FL

Ultraskate is a 24 hour long endurance skateboard challenge that takes place at the Homestead Speedway in southern Florida. Every year people come from all over the world to test their limits and attempt to ride as many miles as they can in the time allotted. During the course of this event, there are many challenges that a competitor has to overcome. Sometimes these challenges are unexpected and it falls on the individual to correctly assess the situation and provide the best possible solution. All of this has to be done while riding a skateboard for 24 hours. The Ultraskate gives an opportunity for individuals to perform a "hard reset" and gain introspection on their personal lives while also providing a grueling physical experience that some find irresistible.

Personal Accolades - 170 miles (2015), 126 miles (2016), 257 miles (2017), 207 miles (2018), 210 miles (2019), 243 miles (2020)

### Chief Ladiga-Silver Comet 188 mile Skate Challenge

Atlanta, GA

The CLSC Skate Challenge is a 188 mile race that takes place over the course of 3 days. Day 1 is ~37 miles, followed by day 2 at ~56 miles. At this point, racers have crossed a state line (and a timezone) to end up in Anniston, AL. On day 3, riders set out at the crack of dawn to complete the entire length of the trail at ~94 miles. The event is done in pure sport and passion for self-induced suffering.

• **Personal Accolade s** - completed the challenge in 2015, 2017, 2018 among the top 5 competitors

### **Athletic Organizations**

- · IDSA (International Distance Skateboarding Association)
- · Shralper's Union
- · Power Plant Board Company

#### Other events

- · Broadway Bomb in New York City, NY
- · Push in the Woods in Portland, OR
- Centennial SK8 Festival in Arlingotn, WA
- · Kick for Cancer in Philadelphia, PA